<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<feed>
<entry>
<title>The Memoirs of Sherlock Holmes</title>
<id>http://www.feedbooks.com/book/58</id>
<author>
<name>Arthur Conan Doyle</name>
<uri>http://www.feedbooks.com/author/1</uri>
</author>
<dcterms:language>en</dcterms:language>
<dcterms:issued>1893</dcterms:issued>
<category term="Collections"/>
<summary>The Memoirs of Sherlock Holmes is a collection of Sherlock Holmes stories, originally published in 1894, by Arthur Conan Doyle.</summary>
<link href="http://www.feedbooks.com/book/58.epub" type="application/epub+zip"/>
<link href="http://www.feedbooks.com/book/58.pdf" type="application/pdf"/>
<link href="http://www.feedbooks.com/book/58.png?size=smaller&amp;t=20091217011415" type="image/png"/>
</entry>
<entry>
<title>The Land of Mist</title>
<id>http://www.feedbooks.com/book/353</id>
<author>
<name>Arthur Conan Doyle</name>
<uri>http://www.feedbooks.com/author/1</uri>
</author>
<dcterms:language>en</dcterms:language>
<dcterms:issued>1926</dcterms:issued>
<category term="Science Fiction"/>
<summary>Heavily influenced by Doyle's growing belief in Spiritualism after the death of his son, brother, and two nephews in World War I, the book focuses on Edward Malone's at first professional, and later personal interest in Spiritualism.</summary>
<link href="http://www.feedbooks.com/book/353.epub" type="application/epub+zip"/>
<link href="http://www.feedbooks.com/book/353.pdf" type="application/pdf"/>
<link href="http://www.feedbooks.com/book/353.png?size=smaller&amp;t=20090916101819" type="image/png"/>
</entry>
<entry>
<title>Les Mémoires de Sherlock Holmes</title>
<id>http://www.feedbooks.com/book/3135</id>
<author>
<name>Arthur Conan Doyle</name>
<uri>http://www.feedbooks.com/author/1</uri>
</author>
<dcterms:language>fr</dcterms:language>
<dcterms:issued>1893</dcterms:issued>
<category term="Collections"/>
<summary>Les mémoires de Sherlock Holmes (The memoirs of Sherlock Holmes) est un recueil de nouvelles policières avec comme héros Sherlock Holmes écrit par Sir Arthur Conan Doyle entre 1892 et 1893.</summary>
<link href="http://www.feedbooks.com/book/3135.epub" type="application/epub+zip"/>
<link href="http://www.feedbooks.com/book/3135.pdf" type="application/pdf"/>
<link href="http://www.feedbooks.com/book/3135.png?size=smaller&amp;t=20090916125908" type="image/png"/>
</entry>
<entry>
<title>The Poison Belt</title>
<id>http://www.feedbooks.com/book/352</id>
<author>
<name>Arthur Conan Doyle</name>
<uri>http://www.feedbooks.com/author/1</uri>
</author>
<dcterms:language>en</dcterms:language>
<dcterms:issued>1913</dcterms:issued>
<category term="Science Fiction"/>
<summary>The Poison Belt was the second story, a novella, that Sir Arthur Conan Doyle wrote about Professor Challenger. Written in 1913, roughly a year before the outbreak of World War I, much of it takes place--rather oddly, given that it follows The Lost World, a story set in the jungle--in a room in Challenger's house. This would be the last story written about Challenger until the 1920s, by which time Doyle's spiritualist beliefs had begun to affect his writing.</summary>
<link href="http://www.feedbooks.com/book/352.epub" type="application/epub+zip"/>
<link href="http://www.feedbooks.com/book/352.pdf" type="application/pdf"/>
<link href="http://www.feedbooks.com/book/352.png?size=smaller&amp;t=20090916101816" type="image/png"/>
</entry>
<entry>
<title>Le Signe des quatre</title>
<id>http://www.feedbooks.com/book/3079</id>
<author>
<name>Arthur Conan Doyle</name>
<uri>http://www.feedbooks.com/author/1</uri>
</author>
<dcterms:language>fr</dcterms:language>
<dcterms:issued>1890</dcterms:issued>
<category term="Crime/Mystery"/>
<summary>Le Signe des quatre est la deuxième aventure de Sherlock Holmes, écrite en 1890 par Arthur Conan Doyle.
Le Signe des quatre se déroule en 1888. Son intrigue s'appuie sur l'Inde coloniale, un trésor volé et un pacte secret entre quatre bagnards, et nous présente notamment Mary Morstan, future épouse du docteur Watson, ainsi que Toby, chien au flair très développé.
Arthur Conan Doyle commence à nous y dévoiler les habitudes de Sherlock Holmes, et notamment, son utilisation de drogue pour tromper l'ennui qui l'accable entre deux enquêtes.
</summary>
<link href="http://www.feedbooks.com/book/3079.epub" type="application/epub+zip"/>
<link href="http://www.feedbooks.com/book/3079.pdf" type="application/pdf"/>
<link href="http://www.feedbooks.com/book/3079.png?size=smaller&amp;t=20090916125301" type="image/png"/>
</entry>
<entry>
<title>The Sign of the Four</title>
<id>http://www.feedbooks.com/book/2</id>
<author>
<name>Arthur Conan Doyle</name>
<uri>http://www.feedbooks.com/author/1</uri>
</author>
<dcterms:language>en</dcterms:language>
<dcterms:issued>1890</dcterms:issued>
<category term="Crime/Mystery"/>
<summary>First published in 1890, The Sign of Four is Sir Arthur Conan Doyle's second book starring legendary detective Sherlock Holmes. The story is complex, involving a secret between four ex-cons from India and a hidden treasure. More complex than the first Holmes novel, The Sign of Four also introduces the detective's drug habit and leaves breadcrumbs for the reader that lead toward the final resolution.</summary>
<link href="http://www.feedbooks.com/book/2.epub" type="application/epub+zip"/>
<link href="http://www.feedbooks.com/book/2.pdf" type="application/pdf"/>
<link href="http://www.feedbooks.com/book/2.png?size=smaller&amp;t=20090916100620" type="image/png"/>
</entry>
<entry>
<title>The Return of Sherlock Holmes</title>
<id>http://www.feedbooks.com/book/63</id>
<author>
<name>Arthur Conan Doyle</name>
<uri>http://www.feedbooks.com/author/1</uri>
</author>
<dcterms:language>en</dcterms:language>
<dcterms:issued>1905</dcterms:issued>
<category term="Collections"/>
<summary>The Return of Sherlock Holmes is a collection of 13 Sherlock Holmes stories, originally published in 1903-1904, by Arthur Conan Doyle.
The book was first published on March 7, 1905 by Georges Newnes, Ltd and in a Colonial edition by Longmans. 30,000 copies were made of the initial print run. The US edition by McClure, Phillips &amp; Co. added another 28,000 to the run.
This was the first Holmes collection since 1893, when Holmes had "died" in "The Adventure of the Final Problem". Having published The Hound of the Baskervilles in 1901–1902 (although setting it before Holmes' death) Doyle came under intense pressure to revive his famous character.</summary>
<link href="http://www.feedbooks.com/book/63.epub" type="application/epub+zip"/>
<link href="http://www.feedbooks.com/book/63.pdf" type="application/pdf"/>
<link href="http://www.feedbooks.com/book/63.png?size=smaller&amp;t=20091203173026" type="image/png"/>
</entry>
<entry>
<title>The Lost World</title>
<id>http://www.feedbooks.com/book/67</id>
<author>
<name>Arthur Conan Doyle</name>
<uri>http://www.feedbooks.com/author/1</uri>
</author>
<dcterms:language>en</dcterms:language>
<dcterms:issued>1912</dcterms:issued>
<category term="Adventure"/>
<summary>The Lost World is a novel released in 1912 by Arthur Conan Doyle concerning an expedition to a plateau in South America where prehistoric animals (dinosaurs and other extinct creatures) still survive. The character of Professor Challenger was introduced in this book. Interestingly, for a seminal work of dinosaur-related fiction, the animals only occupy a small portion of the narrative. Much more time is devoted to a war between early human hominids and a vicious tribe of ape-like creatures.</summary>
<link href="http://www.feedbooks.com/book/67.epub" type="application/epub+zip"/>
<link href="http://www.feedbooks.com/book/67.pdf" type="application/pdf"/>
<link href="http://www.feedbooks.com/book/67.png?size=smaller&amp;t=20090916100805" type="image/png"/>
</entry>
<entry>
<title>The Adventures of Sherlock Holmes</title>
<id>http://www.feedbooks.com/book/1421</id>
<author>
<name>Arthur Conan Doyle</name>
<uri>http://www.feedbooks.com/author/1</uri>
</author>
<dcterms:language>en</dcterms:language>
<dcterms:issued>1892</dcterms:issued>
<category term="Collections"/>
<summary>The Adventures of Sherlock Holmes is a collection of twelve stories by Sir Arthur Conan Doyle, featuring his famous detective and illustrated by Sidney Paget.
These are the first of the Sherlock Holmes short stories, originally published as single stories in the Strand Magazine from July 1891 to June 1892. The book was published in England on October 14, 1892 by George Newnes Ltd and in a US Edition on October 15 by Harper. The initial combined print run was 14,500 copies.</summary>
<link href="http://www.feedbooks.com/book/1421.epub" type="application/epub+zip"/>
<link href="http://www.feedbooks.com/book/1421.pdf" type="application/pdf"/>
<link href="http://www.feedbooks.com/book/1421.png?size=smaller&amp;t=20090916105038" type="image/png"/>
</entry>
<entry>
<title>Le Chien des Baskerville</title>
<id>http://www.feedbooks.com/book/3085</id>
<author>
<name>Arthur Conan Doyle</name>
<uri>http://www.feedbooks.com/author/1</uri>
</author>
<dcterms:language>fr</dcterms:language>
<dcterms:issued>1902</dcterms:issued>
<category term="Crime/Mystery"/>
<summary>Le Chien des Baskerville (The Hound of the Baskervilles) est un roman policier anglais d'Arthur Conan Doyle, publié pour la première fois dans le Strand Magazine en 1901 et 1902.
La légende court dans cette région du Devonshire (sud ouest de l'Angleterre), qu'un énorme chien crachant du feu de sa gueule béante serait à l'origine de la mort de Sir Charles Baskerville. Un de ses ancêtres, Sir Hugo Baskerville, trouva la mort mystérieusement après avoir commis d'immondes atrocités envers une jeune paysanne. Sherlock Holmes et le Docteur Watson enquêtent. Ils doivent protéger le dernier descendant des Baskerville revenu prestement du Canada, Sir Henry, qui lui ne croît pas à toutes ces balivernes.
</summary>
<link href="http://www.feedbooks.com/book/3085.epub" type="application/epub+zip"/>
<link href="http://www.feedbooks.com/book/3085.pdf" type="application/pdf"/>
<link href="http://www.feedbooks.com/book/3085.png?size=smaller&amp;t=20090916125344" type="image/png"/>
</entry>
<entry>
<title>Les Aventures de Sherlock Holmes</title>
<id>http://www.feedbooks.com/book/3133</id>
<author>
<name>Arthur Conan Doyle</name>
<uri>http://www.feedbooks.com/author/1</uri>
</author>
<dcterms:language>fr</dcterms:language>
<dcterms:issued>1892</dcterms:issued>
<category term="Collections"/>
<summary>Les Aventures de Sherlock Holmes sont un recueil de nouvelles policières écrit par Sir Arthur Conan Doyle et mettant en scène son célèbre détective privé. Le livre original a été illustré par Sidney Paget.
Ce sont les premières aventures de Sherlock Holmes. Elles ont été publiées originellement dans Strand Magazine entre juillet 1891 et juin 1892. Le recueil a été publié en Angleterre le 14 octobre 1892 par l’éditeur George Newnes Ldt. Le tirage initial a été de 14 500 exemplaires.
Le livre a été interdit en Union soviétique en 1929 pour raison d'occultisme même si le livre ne livre aucune trace d’une telle thématique.</summary>
<link href="http://www.feedbooks.com/book/3133.epub" type="application/epub+zip"/>
<link href="http://www.feedbooks.com/book/3133.pdf" type="application/pdf"/>
<link href="http://www.feedbooks.com/book/3133.png?size=smaller&amp;t=20090916125900" type="image/png"/>
</entry>
<entry>
<title>A Study in Scarlet</title>
<id>http://www.feedbooks.com/book/57</id>
<author>
<name>Arthur Conan Doyle</name>
<uri>http://www.feedbooks.com/author/1</uri>
</author>
<dcterms:language>en</dcterms:language>
<dcterms:issued>1887</dcterms:issued>
<category term="Crime/Mystery"/>
<summary>A Study in Scarlet is a detective mystery novel written by Sir Arthur Conan Doyle, which was first published in 1887. It is the first story to feature the character of Sherlock Holmes, who would later become one of the most famous and iconic literary detective characters, with long-lasting interest and appeal. The book's title derives from a speech given by Holmes to his companion Doctor Watson on the nature of his work, in which he describes the story's murder investigation as his "study in scarlet": "There’s the scarlet thread of murder running through the colourless skein of life, and our duty is to unravel it, and isolate it, and expose every inch of it."</summary>
<link href="http://www.feedbooks.com/book/57.epub" type="application/epub+zip"/>
<link href="http://www.feedbooks.com/book/57.pdf" type="application/pdf"/>
<link href="http://www.feedbooks.com/book/57.png?size=smaller&amp;t=20090916100754" type="image/png"/>
</entry>
<entry>
<title>His Last Bow</title>
<id>http://www.feedbooks.com/book/65</id>
<author>
<name>Arthur Conan Doyle</name>
<uri>http://www.feedbooks.com/author/1</uri>
</author>
<dcterms:language>en</dcterms:language>
<dcterms:issued>1917</dcterms:issued>
<category term="Collections"/>
<summary>His Last Bow is a collection of seven Sherlock Holmes stories (eight in American editions) by Arthur Conan Doyle, as well as the title of one of the stories in that collection. Originally published in 1917, it contains the various Holmes stories published between 1908 and 1913, as well as the one-off title story from 1917.
The collection was originally called Reminiscences of Sherlock Holmes and did not contain the actual story His Last Bow, which appeared later, after the full-length The Valley of Fear was published. However later editions added it and changed the title. Some recent complete editions have restored the earlier title.
When the Memoirs of Sherlock Holmes were published in the USA for the first time, the publishers believed "The Adventure of the Cardboard Box" was too scandalous for the American public, since it dealt with the theme of adultery. As a result, this story was not published in the USA until many years later, when it was added to His Last Bow. Even today, most American editions of the canon include it with His Last Bow, while most British editions keep the story in its original place in The Memoirs of Sherlock Holmes.</summary>
<link href="http://www.feedbooks.com/book/65.epub" type="application/epub+zip"/>
<link href="http://www.feedbooks.com/book/65.pdf" type="application/pdf"/>
<link href="http://www.feedbooks.com/book/65.png?size=smaller&amp;t=20090916100802" type="image/png"/>
</entry>
<entry>
<title>The Public Domain: Enclosing the Commons of the Mind</title>
<id>http://www.feedbooks.com/book/3471</id>
<author>
<name>James Boyle</name>
<uri>http://www.feedbooks.com/author/838</uri>
</author>
<dcterms:language>en</dcterms:language>
<dcterms:issued>2008</dcterms:issued>
<category term="Essay"/>
<summary>In this enlightening book James Boyle describes what he calls the range wars of the information age—today’s heated battles over intellectual property. Boyle argues that just as every informed citizen needs to know at least something about the environment or civil rights, every citizen should also understand intellectual property law. Why? Because intellectual property rights mark out the ground rules of the information society, and today’s policies are unbalanced, unsupported by evidence, and often detrimental to cultural access, free speech, digital creativity, and scientific innovation.
Boyle identifies as a major problem the widespread failure to understand the importance of the public domain—the realm of material that everyone is free to use and share without permission or fee. The public domain is as vital to innovation and culture as the realm of material protected by intellectual property rights, he asserts, and he calls for a movement akin to the environmental movement to preserve it. With a clear analysis of issues ranging from Jefferson’s philosophy of innovation to musical sampling, synthetic biology and Internet file sharing, this timely book brings a positive new perspective to important cultural and legal debates. If we continue to enclose the “commons of the mind,” Boyle argues, we will all be the poorer.</summary>
<link href="http://feedbooks.com/book/3471.epub" type="application/epub+zip"/>
<link href="http://feedbooks.com/book/3471.pdf" type="application/pdf"/>
<link href="http://feedbooks.com/book/3471.png?size=smaller&amp;t=20090818011807" type="image/png"/>
</entry>
<entry>
<title>Hooking Up</title>
<id>http://www.feedbooks.com/book/2817</id>
<author>
<name>Tom Doyle</name>
<uri>http://www.feedbooks.com/author/529</uri>
</author>
<dcterms:language>en</dcterms:language>
<dcterms:issued>2006</dcterms:issued>
<category term="Science Fiction"/>
<summary>High school and evolution, VR space, artificial intelligence and the unrestrained id.</summary>
<link href="http://www.feedbooks.com/book/2817.epub" type="application/epub+zip"/>
<link href="http://www.feedbooks.com/book/2817.pdf" type="application/pdf"/>
<link href="http://www.feedbooks.com/book/2817.png?size=smaller&amp;t=20090916122726" type="image/png"/>
</entry>
<entry>
<title>Un escándalo en Bohemia</title>
<id>http://www.feedbooks.com/book/3390</id>
<author>
<name>Arthur Conan Doyle</name>
<uri>http://www.feedbooks.com/author/1</uri>
</author>
<dcterms:language>es</dcterms:language>
<dcterms:issued>1891</dcterms:issued>
<category term="Crime/Mystery"/>
<summary>No description available.</summary>
<link href="http://www.feedbooks.com/book/3390.epub" type="application/epub+zip"/>
<link href="http://www.feedbooks.com/book/3390.pdf" type="application/pdf"/>
<link href="http://www.feedbooks.com/book/3390.png?size=smaller&amp;t=20090818011805" type="image/png"/>
</entry>
<entry>
<title>El anillo de Thoth</title>
<id>http://www.feedbooks.com/book/3391</id>
<author>
<name>Arthur Conan Doyle</name>
<uri>http://www.feedbooks.com/author/1</uri>
</author>
<dcterms:language>es</dcterms:language>
<dcterms:issued>1890</dcterms:issued>
<category term="Horror"/>
<summary>No description available.</summary>
<link href="http://www.feedbooks.com/book/3391.epub" type="application/epub+zip"/>
<link href="http://www.feedbooks.com/book/3391.pdf" type="application/pdf"/>
<link href="http://www.feedbooks.com/book/3391.png?size=smaller&amp;t=20090818011805" type="image/png"/>
</entry>
<entry>
<title>Lote número 249</title>
<id>http://www.feedbooks.com/book/3392</id>
<author>
<name>Arthur Conan Doyle</name>
<uri>http://www.feedbooks.com/author/1</uri>
</author>
<dcterms:language>es</dcterms:language>
<dcterms:issued>1892</dcterms:issued>
<category term="Horror"/>
<summary>No description available.</summary>
<link href="http://www.feedbooks.com/book/3392.epub" type="application/epub+zip"/>
<link href="http://www.feedbooks.com/book/3392.pdf" type="application/pdf"/>
<link href="http://www.feedbooks.com/book/3392.png?size=smaller&amp;t=20090818011805" type="image/png"/>
</entry>
<entry>
<title>Le Retour de Sherlock Holmes</title>
<id>http://www.feedbooks.com/book/3655</id>
<author>
<name>Arthur Conan Doyle</name>
<uri>http://www.feedbooks.com/author/1</uri>
</author>
<dcterms:language>fr</dcterms:language>
<dcterms:issued>1904</dcterms:issued>
<category term="Collections"/>
<summary>No description available.</summary>
<link href="http://www.feedbooks.com/book/3655.epub" type="application/epub+zip"/>
<link href="http://www.feedbooks.com/book/3655.pdf" type="application/pdf"/>
<link href="http://www.feedbooks.com/book/3655.png?size=smaller&amp;t=20090818011811" type="image/png"/>
</entry>
<entry>
<title>Son Dernier Coup d’Archet</title>
<id>http://www.feedbooks.com/book/3656</id>
<author>
<name>Arthur Conan Doyle</name>
<uri>http://www.feedbooks.com/author/1</uri>
</author>
<dcterms:language>fr</dcterms:language>
<dcterms:issued>1917</dcterms:issued>
<category term="Collections"/>
<summary>Un recueil de nouvelles racontant les dernières aventures de Sherlock Holmes.</summary>
<link href="http://www.feedbooks.com/book/3656.epub" type="application/epub+zip"/>
<link href="http://www.feedbooks.com/book/3656.pdf" type="application/pdf"/>
<link href="http://www.feedbooks.com/book/3656.png?size=smaller&amp;t=20090818011811" type="image/png"/>
</entry>
<entry>
<title>Les Archives de Sherlock Holmes</title>
<id>http://www.feedbooks.com/book/3657</id>
<author>
<name>Arthur Conan Doyle</name>
<uri>http://www.feedbooks.com/author/1</uri>
</author>
<dcterms:language>fr</dcterms:language>
<dcterms:issued>1927</dcterms:issued>
<category term="Collections"/>
<summary>No description available.</summary>
<link href="http://www.feedbooks.com/book/3657.epub" type="application/epub+zip"/>
<link href="http://www.feedbooks.com/book/3657.pdf" type="application/pdf"/>
<link href="http://www.feedbooks.com/book/3657.png?size=smaller&amp;t=20090818011811" type="image/png"/>
</entry>
<entry>
<title>The Valley of Fear</title>
<id>http://www.feedbooks.com/book/64</id>
<author>
<name>Arthur Conan Doyle</name>
<uri>http://www.feedbooks.com/author/1</uri>
</author>
<dcterms:language>en</dcterms:language>
<dcterms:issued>1915</dcterms:issued>
<category term="Crime/Mystery"/>
<summary>The plot of the novel is based very loosely on the real-life activities of the Molly Maguires and, particularly, of Pinkerton agent James McParland.
The novel is divided into two parts: in the first, Holmes investigates an apparent murder and discovers that the body belongs to another man; and in the second, the story of the man originally thought to have been the victim is told.</summary>
<link href="http://www.feedbooks.com/book/64.epub" type="application/epub+zip"/>
<link href="http://www.feedbooks.com/book/64.pdf" type="application/pdf"/>
<link href="http://www.feedbooks.com/book/64.png?size=smaller&amp;t=20090916100800" type="image/png"/>
</entry>
<entry>
<title>The Disintegration Machine</title>
<id>http://www.feedbooks.com/book/354</id>
<author>
<name>Arthur Conan Doyle</name>
<uri>http://www.feedbooks.com/author/1</uri>
</author>
<dcterms:language>en</dcterms:language>
<dcterms:issued>1928</dcterms:issued>
<category term="Science Fiction"/>
<summary>Professor Challenger is arguing with people who are persistently calling him on the telephone when his young friend Malone, a reporter for the Gazette, enters and requests Challenger accompany him to inspect the discovery of Theodore Nemor, who claims to have invented a machine capable of disintegrating objects. Skeptical of the invention, Challenger accepts Malone's proposal and accompanies him to the house of Nemor.</summary>
<link href="http://www.feedbooks.com/book/354.epub" type="application/epub+zip"/>
<link href="http://www.feedbooks.com/book/354.pdf" type="application/pdf"/>
<link href="http://www.feedbooks.com/book/354.png?size=smaller&amp;t=20090916101819" type="image/png"/>
</entry>
<entry>
<title>When the World Screamed</title>
<id>http://www.feedbooks.com/book/355</id>
<author>
<name>Arthur Conan Doyle</name>
<uri>http://www.feedbooks.com/author/1</uri>
</author>
<dcterms:language>en</dcterms:language>
<dcterms:issued>1929</dcterms:issued>
<category term="Science Fiction"/>
<summary>Professor Challenger drills into the earth until he reaches the mantle, convinced that it is a sentient being and that by doing so he will be the first person to alert it to mankind's presence. He awakens the giant creature, which then proceeds to destroy his machine.</summary>
<link href="http://www.feedbooks.com/book/355.epub" type="application/epub+zip"/>
<link href="http://www.feedbooks.com/book/355.pdf" type="application/pdf"/>
<link href="http://www.feedbooks.com/book/355.png?size=smaller&amp;t=20090916101819" type="image/png"/>
</entry>
<entry>
<title>Through the Magic Door</title>
<id>http://www.feedbooks.com/book/356</id>
<author>
<name>Arthur Conan Doyle</name>
<uri>http://www.feedbooks.com/author/1</uri>
</author>
<dcterms:language>en</dcterms:language>
<dcterms:issued>1907</dcterms:issued>
<category term="Essay"/>
<summary>Essays about books.</summary>
<link href="http://www.feedbooks.com/book/356.epub" type="application/epub+zip"/>
<link href="http://www.feedbooks.com/book/356.pdf" type="application/pdf"/>
<link href="http://www.feedbooks.com/book/356.png?size=smaller&amp;t=20090916101821" type="image/png"/>
</entry>
<entry>
<title>The Mystery of Cloomber</title>
<id>http://www.feedbooks.com/book/359</id>
<author>
<name>Arthur Conan Doyle</name>
<uri>http://www.feedbooks.com/author/1</uri>
</author>
<dcterms:language>en</dcterms:language>
<dcterms:issued>1889</dcterms:issued>
<category term="Crime/Mystery"/>
<summary>Near their residence, Branksome, is The Cloomber Hall, for many years untenanted. After a little while it is settled in by John Berthier Heatherstone, late of the Indian Army. General Heatherstone is nervous to the point of being paranoid. As the story unfolds, it becomes evident that his fears are connected with some people in India whom he has offended somehow. People hear a strange sound, like the tolling of a bell, in his presence, which seems to cause the general great discomfort. Every year his paranoia reaches its climax around the fifth of October, after which date his fears subside for a while. After some time there is a shipwreck in the bay and among the survivors are three Buddhist priests who had boarded the ship from Kurrachee.</summary>
<link href="http://www.feedbooks.com/book/359.epub" type="application/epub+zip"/>
<link href="http://www.feedbooks.com/book/359.pdf" type="application/pdf"/>
<link href="http://www.feedbooks.com/book/359.png?size=smaller&amp;t=20090916101833" type="image/png"/>
</entry>
<entry>
<title>The Great Shadow</title>
<id>http://www.feedbooks.com/book/363</id>
<author>
<name>Arthur Conan Doyle</name>
<uri>http://www.feedbooks.com/author/1</uri>
</author>
<dcterms:language>en</dcterms:language>
<dcterms:issued>1892</dcterms:issued>
<category term="History"/>
<summary>No description available.</summary>
<link href="http://www.feedbooks.com/book/363.epub" type="application/epub+zip"/>
<link href="http://www.feedbooks.com/book/363.pdf" type="application/pdf"/>
<link href="http://www.feedbooks.com/book/363.png?size=smaller&amp;t=20090916101854" type="image/png"/>
</entry>
<entry>
<title>The Exploits of Brigadier Gerard</title>
<id>http://www.feedbooks.com/book/364</id>
<author>
<name>Arthur Conan Doyle</name>
<uri>http://www.feedbooks.com/author/1</uri>
</author>
<dcterms:language>en</dcterms:language>
<dcterms:issued>1896</dcterms:issued>
<category term="War"/>
<summary>No description available.</summary>
<link href="http://www.feedbooks.com/book/364.epub" type="application/epub+zip"/>
<link href="http://www.feedbooks.com/book/364.pdf" type="application/pdf"/>
<link href="http://www.feedbooks.com/book/364.png?size=smaller&amp;t=20090916101857" type="image/png"/>
</entry>
<entry>
<title>Uncle Bernac</title>
<id>http://www.feedbooks.com/book/365</id>
<author>
<name>Arthur Conan Doyle</name>
<uri>http://www.feedbooks.com/author/1</uri>
</author>
<dcterms:language>en</dcterms:language>
<dcterms:issued>1897</dcterms:issued>
<category term="History"/>
<summary>At this unexpected announcement Talleyrand and Berthier looked at each other in silence, and for once the trained features of the great diplomatist, who lived behind a mask, betrayed the fact that he was still capable of emotion. The spasm which passed over them was caused, however, rather by mischievous amusement than by consternation, while Berthier--who had an honest affection for both Napoleon and Josephine-- ran frantically to the door as if to bar the Empress from entering.</summary>
<link href="http://www.feedbooks.com/book/365.epub" type="application/epub+zip"/>
<link href="http://www.feedbooks.com/book/365.pdf" type="application/pdf"/>
<link href="http://www.feedbooks.com/book/365.png?size=smaller&amp;t=20090916101903" type="image/png"/>
</entry>
<entry>
<title>The Adventures of Brigadier Gerard</title>
<id>http://www.feedbooks.com/book/366</id>
<author>
<name>Arthur Conan Doyle</name>
<uri>http://www.feedbooks.com/author/1</uri>
</author>
<dcterms:language>en</dcterms:language>
<dcterms:issued>1903</dcterms:issued>
<category term="War"/>
<summary>No description available.</summary>
<link href="http://www.feedbooks.com/book/366.epub" type="application/epub+zip"/>
<link href="http://www.feedbooks.com/book/366.pdf" type="application/pdf"/>
<link href="http://www.feedbooks.com/book/366.png?size=smaller&amp;t=20090916101907" type="image/png"/>
</entry>
<entry>
<title>La Vallée de la peur</title>
<id>http://www.feedbooks.com/book/3092</id>
<author>
<name>Arthur Conan Doyle</name>
<uri>http://www.feedbooks.com/author/1</uri>
</author>
<dcterms:language>fr</dcterms:language>
<dcterms:issued>1915</dcterms:issued>
<category term="Crime/Mystery"/>
<summary>Sherlock Holmes reçoit un message l’avertissant de l’assassinat d’un certain Douglas de Birlstone Manor House. L’inspecteur Mac Donald de Scotland Yard vient lui annoncer cette même nouvelle. Ils partent donc sur place.
Le mort a été tué d’un coup de winchester sur la figure. Il est méconnaissable. Mais il porte les bagues du maître de maison, sauf son alliance et a ce curieux tatouage à l’avant-bras...</summary>
<link href="http://www.feedbooks.com/book/3092.epub" type="application/epub+zip"/>
<link href="http://www.feedbooks.com/book/3092.pdf" type="application/pdf"/>
<link href="http://www.feedbooks.com/book/3092.png?size=smaller&amp;t=20090916105255" type="image/png"/>
</entry>
<entry>
<title>Une Étude en rouge</title>
<id>http://www.feedbooks.com/book/3078</id>
<author>
<name>Arthur Conan Doyle</name>
<uri>http://www.feedbooks.com/author/1</uri>
</author>
<dcterms:language>fr</dcterms:language>
<dcterms:issued>1887</dcterms:issued>
<category term="Crime/Mystery"/>
<summary>Londres, 1878. Le Dr Watson fait la connaissance de Sherlock Holmes lorsqu'ils décident d'habiter ensemble.
Un jour, Sherlock Holmes reçoit une lettre de Tobias Gregson, un des limiers de Scotland Yard, qui lui demande de l'aide dans une affaire de meurtre...</summary>
<link href="http://www.feedbooks.com/book/3078.epub" type="application/epub+zip"/>
<link href="http://www.feedbooks.com/book/3078.pdf" type="application/pdf"/>
<link href="http://www.feedbooks.com/book/3078.png?size=smaller&amp;t=20090916125255" type="image/png"/>
</entry>
<entry>
<title>The Hound of the Baskervilles</title>
<id>http://www.feedbooks.com/book/1</id>
<author>
<name>Arthur Conan Doyle</name>
<uri>http://www.feedbooks.com/author/1</uri>
</author>
<dcterms:language>en</dcterms:language>
<dcterms:issued>1902</dcterms:issued>
<category term="Crime/Mystery"/>
<summary>The rich landowner Sir Charles Baskerville is found dead in the park of his manor surrounded by the grim moor of Dartmoor, in the county of Devon. His death seems to have been caused by a heart attack, but the victim's best friend, Dr. Mortimer, is convinced that the strike was due to a supernatural creature, which haunts the moor in the shape of an enormous hound, with blazing eyes and jaws. In order to protect Baskerville's heir, Sir Henry, who's arriving to London from Canada, Dr. Mortimer asks for Sherlock Holmes' help, telling him also of the so-called Baskervilles' curse, according to which a monstrous hound has been haunting and killing the family males for centuries, in revenge for the misdeeds of one Sir Hugo Baskerville, who lived at the time of Oliver Cromwell. </summary>
<link href="http://www.feedbooks.com/book/1.epub" type="application/epub+zip"/>
<link href="http://www.feedbooks.com/book/1.pdf" type="application/pdf"/>
<link href="http://www.feedbooks.com/book/1.png?size=smaller&amp;t=20090917111326" type="image/png"/>
</entry>
<entry>
<title>The Casebook of Sherlock Holmes</title>
<id>http://www.feedbooks.com/book/66</id>
<author>
<name>Arthur Conan Doyle</name>
<uri>http://www.feedbooks.com/author/1</uri>
</author>
<dcterms:language>en</dcterms:language>
<dcterms:issued>1923</dcterms:issued>
<category term="Collections"/>
<summary>The last twelve stories written about Holmes and Watson, these tales reflect the disillusioned world of the 1920s in which they were written. Some of the sharpest turns of wit in English literature are contrasted by dark images of psychological tragedy, suicide, and incest in a collection of tales that have haunted generations of readers.</summary>
<link href="http://www.feedbooks.com/book/66.epub" type="application/epub+zip"/>
<link href="http://www.feedbooks.com/book/66.pdf" type="application/pdf"/>
<link href="http://www.feedbooks.com/book/66.png?size=smaller&amp;t=20091203173128" type="image/png"/>
</entry>
<entry>
<title>The Land That Time Forgot</title>
<id>http://www.feedbooks.com/book/188</id>
<author>
<name>Edgar Rice Burroughs</name>
<uri>http://www.feedbooks.com/author/23</uri>
</author>
<dcterms:language>en</dcterms:language>
<dcterms:issued>1918</dcterms:issued>
<category term="Science Fiction"/>
<summary>Starting out as a harrowing wartime sea adventure, Burroughs’s story ultimately develops into a lost world story reminiscent of such novels as Sir Arthur Conan Doyle’s The Lost World (1912) and Jules Verne’s The Mysterious Island (1874) and Journey to the Center of the Earth (1864). Burroughs adds his own twist by postulating a unique biological system for his lost world, in which the slow progress of evolution in the world outside is recapitulated as a matter of individual metamorphosis.</summary>
<link href="http://www.feedbooks.com/book/188.epub" type="application/epub+zip"/>
<link href="http://www.feedbooks.com/book/188.pdf" type="application/pdf"/>
<link href="http://www.feedbooks.com/book/188.png?size=smaller&amp;t=20090916101303" type="image/png"/>
</entry>
<entry>
<title>Nouvelles Mille et une nuits</title>
<id>http://www.feedbooks.com/book/3372</id>
<author>
<name>Robert Louis Stevenson</name>
<uri>http://www.feedbooks.com/author/37</uri>
</author>
<dcterms:language>fr</dcterms:language>
<dcterms:issued>1882</dcterms:issued>
<category term="Collections"/>
<summary>Pourquoi ce titre? Parce que chaque nouvelle, articulée en épisodes, de ce recueil, apporte quelque chose à l'histoire globale et l'enrichit, et que le narrateur, tel Shéhérazade, incite le lecteur à lire la suite pour avoir les clés de l'histoire dont il vient de lui être fait lecture. Ne sont malheureusement présentées ici que deux nouvelles. Nous sommes à Londres, à la fin du XIXe siècle, nous cotoyons souvent les bas-fonds noyés dans le brouillard de cette société et l'atmosphère de ces nouvelles est caractéristique de ce lieu, de cette époque, comme pour d'autres écrivains, Arthur Conan Doyle en particulier.</summary>
<link href="http://feedbooks.com/book/3372.epub" type="application/epub+zip"/>
<link href="http://feedbooks.com/book/3372.pdf" type="application/pdf"/>
<link href="http://feedbooks.com/book/3372.png?size=smaller&amp;t=20090818011804" type="image/png"/>
</entry>
<entry>
<title>The Triumphs of Eugène Valmont</title>
<id>http://www.feedbooks.com/book/3734</id>
<author>
<name>Robert Barr</name>
<uri>http://www.feedbooks.com/author/980</uri>
</author>
<dcterms:language>en</dcterms:language>
<dcterms:issued>1906</dcterms:issued>
<category term="Humor/Satire"/>
<summary>The Triumphs of Eugene Valmont (1906) brings together tales of the multifarious exploits of Robert Barr's elegant and cunning sleuth, Valmont, a brilliantly ironic parody of Sherlock Holmes. Exhibiting the crucial combination of realism and imagination that characterizes the finest crime writing, the stories exude playfulness and blend mystery and quasi-Gothic thrills with humorous detours and romantic adventure. A notable figure in 1890s literary London and a friend of Conan Doyle, Barr was acutely aware of style as a form of statement and the stories are full of literary effects, commentary on the detective mystery genre, and Valmont's disparaging reflections on English values.</summary>
<link href="http://www.feedbooks.com/book/3734.epub" type="application/epub+zip"/>
<link href="http://www.feedbooks.com/book/3734.pdf" type="application/pdf"/>
<link href="http://www.feedbooks.com/book/3734.png?size=smaller&amp;t=20090818011812" type="image/png"/>
</entry>
</feed>
